You wanted power You wanted clean A hollow sound
from a thin machine You tried to tune me out You
tried to change the dial But I've been waiting
all this while
I am the static, I am the noise The signal
breaking, the hidden voice I am the static, the
feedback whale The story that you try to derail
This isn't simple, this isn't grace. This is the
sound of a different place. This is the heart you
tried to hide. The five of us have never died. I am
the static, I am the noise, the signal breaking,
the hidden voice. I am the static, the feedback
whale, the story that you try to derail.
Come on.
I am the static, I am the noise, the signal
breaking, the hidden voice. I am the static, the
feedback whale, the story that you try to
derail. I am the static, I am the static Can you
hear me now?